(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-08T06:28:34.168114",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Bau bau! Bau bau! Bau bau!
I know that you were waiting! I'm Fuwawa!
I know who you are! I'm Mococo!
Together we're hololive English - Advent's twin demon guard sisters, we're...
FUWAMOCO! Bau bau!
Can you believe it? Finally here, together in 3D!
Yeah, and just for today, for this special occasion...
We're back home here in the North-West Passages in the Macabee!
We're back home here in the North-West Passages in the Macabee! Bau bau!
Yeah, all Ruffians!
Yeah, this is the... this is the...
The Abyss Garden! Can you believe it?
It's nice, right? This is the place that these puppies grew up!
Yeah! I know, I'm so excited! We're finally 3D today in 3D, but um, I have to tell the two...
I'm a bit nervous, huh? Is it okay if I hide behind you, Fuwawa?
Of course not, Mococo! You can't, okay?
This is our chance to show the Ruffians just how fluffy and fluffy we are, you know?
Okay, I'll do my best then! Ruffians, we have so much to show you!
But I know something that will help me calm down a bit. Ruffians, can you do me a favor? Please!
Well, can you tweet out with the hashtag #FWMC3D?
#FWMC3D! #FWMC3D!
Please share your thoughts and your favorite moments from today with us, okay? We're going to find down, tweet down!
Oh wait, go ahead! Oh!
What? What? What?
That's how it chooses.
What? I'm so nervous! I'm so nervous, boy!
Can you? Can you do the thing? The thing?
The thing?
Oh, okay.
Okay, Mococo-chan, are you ready?
Yeah.
Okay.
Hey!
Good. Now, whose turn?
My turn.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Turn around, turn around.
Is this just because you want to hit me?
No, it's okay.
Okay.
Okay, here we go.
Hey!
Maybe I'm a bit better now.
Yeah, I think she's okay.
If we're ready now, maybe we can share a song with everyone.
Our first song for today. Yeah, you know, it's a very important song to us. Our very own original introduction song, okay?
Please dance along.
Bow wow with us, okay?
Lifetime showtime!
it's showtime!
一緒にいたいよ
I want to be together with you!
lifetime showtime
anytime bau bau!
yeah, future is bright
Yeah, the future is bright,
(yeah 二人は)
(Yeah, as twins)
fluffy fuzzy yappy sisters!
fuwa! moco!
(bau bau bau bau!)
my heart n' soul n' tail are fuwawa
i'm so fluffy that even i could float away
just call for me, we're only a bark away
your smile is the treasure that i wanna keep safe
fuwa! moco!
i love being tricky
doggy kisses are for me
i love lots of walkies
don't need no leashes for me
silly puppy mococo will follow you anywhere
fuwamoco together, take us along with you
barking oh so merrily!
it's showtime!
一緒にいたい (oh!)
I want to be together (Oh!)
lifetime showtime
anytime bau bau!
一生涯 sing with you
For a lifetime, sing with you!
stars wink
moon spotlight
furr-ever glow
it's showtime!
一緒にいたいよ
I want to be together with you,
lifetime showtime
anytime bau bau!
yeah, future is bright
Yeah, the future is bright,
(yeah 二人は)
(Yeah, as twins)
fluffy fuzzy yappy sisters!
bau! woooo…
Bau! Woooo...
bau!
way back then, all locked up, we were stuck in the cell
holding back, doggy dog kept sealed away
bau!
bouta burst, fluff & fuzz we're meant to be free
make a break for it
it's playtime!
paws hitting the pavement
dreams sparklin' within our eyes
gonna keep you smilin'
but my sneezes won't stop flyin' by
even though we're still just a pair of scaredy puppy dogs
the bond that we share as twins is irreplaceable
we're a pair unbreakable!
and that's why
いつだって
every single day,
it's that day! (today!)
lifetime! showtime!
not tomorrow! bau bau!
一生涯 walk with you!
For a lifetime, walk with you!
good times and
bad times
it doesn't matter!
いつだって
Every single day,
it's that day!
lifetime showtime
everyday! bau bau!
yeah 二人は
Yeah, as twins,
happy lucky puppy sisters!
fuwamoco bau bau!
everybody, bau bau!
hallo hallo bau bau!
ダメダメ ノンノン!
No-no, non-non!
don't touch the ears!
もふもふ ノンノン!
Fluff-fluff, non-non!
don't touch the tail!
チワワじゃないよ! フワだよ! bau!
I'm not a Chihuahua! I'm Fuwa! Bau!
チワワじゃないよ! モコだよ! bau!
I'm not a Chihuahua! I'm Moco! Bau!
twin demon guard dog sisters, yeah! bau!
and together, we're…
And together, we're...
fuwamoco!
gather up our dreams
and suddenly you'll come to realize
there's as many as there are stars
illuminating the night sky
never-ending dreams
we don't know if they all can be achieved
but we'll keep on going furr-ever
together here with you!
it's showtime
一緒にいたい fufu!
I want to be together, fufu!
it's showtime
一緒にいたい fufu!
I want to be together, fufu!
it's showtime
一緒にいたいよ
I want to be together with you!
fuwa fuwa
moco moco
hand in hand with you
bring your smile, rain or shine
we'll protect it
won't forget our pledge to you!
it's showtime!
一緒にいたい (oh!)
I want to be together (Oh!)
lifetime showtime
anytime bau bau!
一生涯 sing with you
For a lifetime, sing with you!
stars wink
moon spotlight
furr-ever glow
it's showtime!
一緒にいたいよ
I want to be together with you,
lifetime showtime
anytime bau bau!
and together, we're…
And together, we're...
fluffy fuzzy yappy sisters!
fuwa! moco!
fuwamoco (bau bau)
Bau bau! Thank you so much!
You know, it means so much to us to...
It's showtime!
一緒にいたいよ
We want to be together...
Lifetime showtime
Anytime bau bau!
Yeah, future is bright
Yeah, the future is bright!
Fluffy fuzzy yappy sisters!
Fuwa! Moco!
(Bau bau bau bau!)
My heart n' soul n' tail are fuwawa
I'm so fluffy that even i could float away
Just call for me, we're only a bark away
Your smile is the treasure that i wanna keep safe
Fuwa! Moco!
I love being tricky
Doggy kisses are for me
I love lots of walkies
Don't need no leashes for me
Silly puppy mococo will follow you anywhere
Fuwamoco together, take us along with you
Barking oh so merrily!
It's showtime!
一緒にいたい
We want to be together...
Lifetime showtime
Anytime bau bau!
生涯
For a lifetime,
Sing with you
Stars wink
Moon spotlight
Furr-ever glow
It's showtime!
一緒にいたいよ
We want to be together!
Lifetime showtime
Anytime bau bau!
Yeah, future is bright
Yeah, the future is bright!
（Yeah 二人は）
(Yeah, the two of us are)
Fluffy fuzzy yappy sisters!
Bau! Woooo...
Bau!
Way back then, all locked up, we were stuck in the cell
Holding back, doggy dog kept sealed away
Bau!
Bouta burst, fluff & fuzz we're meant to be free
Make a break for it
make a break for it—
It's playtime!
Paws hitting the pavement
Dreams sparklin' within our eyes
Gonna keep you smilin'
But my sneezes won't stop fly in' by
but my sneezes won't stop flyin' by!
Even though we're still just a pair of scaredy puppy dogs
The bond that we share as twins is irreplaceable
the bond that we share as twins is irreplaceable—
We're a pair unbreakable!
And that's why
いつだって
It's always...
It's that day! (Today!)
Lifetime! Showtime!
Not tomorrow! bau bau!
生涯
For a lifetime,
Walk with you!
Good times and
Bad times
bad times—
It doesn't matter!
いつだって
It's always...
It's that day!
Lifetime showtime
Everyday! bau bau!
Yeah 二人は
Yeah, the two of us are
Happy lucky puppy sisters!
Fuwamoco bau bau!
Everybody, bau bau!
Hallo hallo bau bau!
ダメダメ ノンノン！
Dame dame non non!
Don't touch the ears!
もふもふ ノンノン！
Mofu mofu non non!
Don't touch the tail!
チワワ じゃないよ！ フワワ だよ！ bau！
Not a Chihuahua! I'm Fuwawa! Bau!
チワワ じゃないよ！ モコモコ だよ！ bau！
Not a Chihuahua! I'm Mococo! Bau!
Twin demon guard dog sisters, yeah! bau!
And together, we're…
And together, we're...
Fuwamoco!
Gather up our dreams
And suddenly you'll come to realize
There's as many as there are stars
Illuminating the night sky
Never-ending dreams
We don't know if they all can be achieved
But we'll keep on going furr-ever
Together here with you!
It's showtime
一緒にいたい fufu!
We want to be together, fufu!
It's showtime
一緒にいたい fufu!
We want to be together, fufu!
It's showtime
一緒にいたいよ
We want to be together!
Fuwa fuwa
Moco moco
Hand in hand with you
Bring your smile, rain or shine
We'll protect it
Won't forget our pledge to you!
It's showtime!
一緒にいたい (Oh!)
We want to be together (Oh!)
Lifetime showtime
Anytime bau bau!
生涯
For a lifetime,
Sing with you
Stars wink
Moon spotlight
Furr-ever glow
It's showtime!
一緒にいたいよ
We want to be together!
Lifetime showtime
Anytime bau bau!
And together, we're...
Fluffy fuzzy yappy sisters!
Fuwa! Moco!
Fuwamoco (Bau bau)
My heart n' soul n' tail are fuwawa
I'm so fluffy that even i could float away
Just call for me, we're only a bark away
Your smile is the treasure that i wanna keep safe
Fuwa! Moco!
I love being tricky
Doggy kisses are for me
I love lots of walkies
Don't need no leashes for me
Silly puppy mococo will follow you anywhere
Fuwamoco together, take us along with you
Barking oh so merrily!
It's showtime!
一緒にいたい
We want to be together...
Lifetime showtime
Anytime bau bau!
生涯
For a lifetime,
Sing with you
Stars wink
Moon spotlight
Furr-ever glow
It's showtime!
一緒にいたいよ
We want to be together!
Lifetime showtime
Anytime bau bau!
Yeah, future is bright
Yeah, the future is bright!
（Yeah 二人は）
(Yeah, the two of us are)
Fluffy fuzzy yappy sisters!
Bau! Woooo...
Bau!
Way back then, all locked up, we were stuck in the cell
Holding back, doggy dog kept sealed away
Bau!
Bouta burst, fluff & fuzz we're meant to be free
Make a break for it
make a break for it—
It's playtime!
Paws hitting the pavement
Dreams sparklin' within our eyes
Gonna keep you smilin'
But my sneezes won't stop fly in' by
but my sneezes won't stop flyin' by!
Even though we're still just a pair of scaredy puppy dogs
The bond that we share as twins is irreplaceable
the bond that we share as twins is irreplaceable—
We're a pair unbreakable!
And that's why
いつだって
It's always...
It's that day! (Today!)
Lifetime! Showtime!
Not tomorrow! bau bau!
生涯
For a lifetime,
Walk with you!
Good times and
Bad times
bad times—
It doesn't matter!
いつだって
It's always...
It's that day!
Lifetime showtime
Everyday! bau bau!
Yeah 二人は
Yeah, the two of us are
Happy lucky puppy sisters!
Fuwamoco bau bau!
Everybody, bau bau!
Hallo hallo bau bau!
ダメダメ ノンノン！
Dame dame non non!
Don't touch the ears!
もふもふ ノンノン！
Mofu mofu non non!
Don't touch the tail!
チワワ じゃないよ！ フワワ だよ！ bau！
Not a Chihuahua! I'm Fuwawa! Bau!
Can you? Can you show? Oh! You're so... a really cute!
Can you show? Oh, you're so— Oh, really cute!
Ah, cute poses!
Cute poses? You poses! What do you mean? This isn't cute and now!
Cute poses? What do you mean? This isn't cute enough!
No! Ah!
Show me your cute side!
Ah, mocochat! Ah, ah, ah!
Mocochat! Yay! Cute! Yay, yay, yay!
Ah! Cute! Ah, mocochat!
Oi! Ah, ah, mocochat! Oi!
I had a test today and I got a 100%.
Good job! Yay!
Congratulations! Bow wow!
Ah, ah, mocochat!
Mocochat, can you show us your fuzzy tail?
Tail?
Yeah, like this? Ah, like this?
More fuzzy! More fuzzy! More fuzzy!
Like this? Ah, like this?
Is- is this all that much? Ah, mocochat!
Is— is this all that much? Ah, mocochat!
I want to get a close-up! Why so many close-ups? Ah!
No! No, no, way, too much!
That's enough, okay?
No more! No more! What?
No!
I'm done.
Maybe the Ruffians can tell us the point now!
You better!
Well then...
Okay, shimasu ne. Okki...
But you know...
I guess, if the Ruffians are happy, we're happy.
After all, we're protecting your smiles! Bow wow!
Bow wow! Since we're here, let's show the Ruffians around, mocochat!
Yeah, okay! Here! It's our house!
Yeah, like this! Mention, this is our childcare home...
...here in the Northless Passage!
Yeah, the mokkakai!
What do you think? Pretty like it?
Is it a little bit different than you expected?
It's pretty nice, I mean, don't worry about the paper!
Yeah, you know, we just got into a little bit of fun and mischief.
Well, mama puppy and papa puppy are out home right now.
Yeah, don't worry about that, okay?
Don't bother going in-game today. You can see they're not home, right?
Yeah, the Northless Passage is filled with lots of nature! Let's go take a look around here.
You see, these they go wild, the wild dandeballs!
Bow wow! They're so fluffy! Right?
I love them so much, they're really nice, you know. There's a restaurant of it!
Oh, you know, some people, because they grow wild and everything, they feel like a nuisance.
But we love all of them, and you know, our moons...
Over here, we have two moons.
It's a bit different in the Northless Passage, you know.
And you know, it's because of the twin moons that mama puppy will receive the blessing, and that we're here now.
Don't you think this looks pretty? Just look up with them, and we want to go bow wow!
Oh, this way! We have a stream!
It's really fun playing it on hot days sometimes, so many memories, right?
And back over this way!
Be howl!
Bow wow!
Right here, this is our legendary tree of progress!
A very special part of our home, you know, we can't- we can't be without it, right?
A very special part of our home, you know, we can't— we can't be without it, right?
And actually, it's even more beautiful at night, but you'll just have to take our word for it!
Yeah, okay! Bow wow!
Bow wow!
We're so happy to be able to share our home like this with you.
Yes! You're so special, and I'm looking forward to making so many more memories with you!
Yeah!
This could be no other than what you got in that Korea... wait!
It's I! The great Peratcino!
Perat- Are you here to ruin our 3D debut, bow wow?
Perat— are you here to ruin our 3D debut, bow wow?
Nah! I never do anything of the sort! After all, the star of the show is finally here!
You were meant to the great Peratcino!
The Ruffians have been waiting for me! Don't you hear it?
They're chanting my name! Bow wow!
Well, we're just opening act then! Bow wow!
Perat, you're just our pet, okay?
And a nasty one at that, okay? You're not the star!
No, I think it's time! We put you in your place!
Ha! Catch me! Yeah, mocochat! Yay!
こんな感じ？
"Can we do it like this?"
はっ！
"Hah!"
食らえ！
"Take this!"
はっ！
"Hah!"
いたっ！
"Ouch!"
はっ！
"Hah!"
どーん！
"Bam!"
はっ！食らえ！
"Hah! Take this!"
はっ！はっ！
"Hah! Hah!"
はっ！
"Hah!"
どん！どん！
"Bam! Bam!"
もくちゃん、なんかふかふか！
"Mogu-chan, you're not as fluffy!"
な、ない！ふかふかは私！
"No, I'm fluffier than you!"
はっ！
"Hah!"
キャッチ！
"Catch!"
はっ！そんなに引っ張らないで！
"Hah! Don't pull so hard!"
はっ！どうだ！
"Hah! How's that!"
給料もっとぱんち！
"Give 'em a few punches!"
はっ！はっ！
"Hah! Hah!"
はっ！食らえ！はっ！
"Hah! Take this! Hah!"
どーん！
"Take that!"
ストップ！ストップ！
"Stop! Stop!"
はっ！ストップ！
"Hah! Stop!"
まあ、慈悲を見せよう。はっ！
"Well, I'll show you mercy. Hah!"
でも、私達超強い、でしょ？はっ！
"But we're super strong, right? Hah!"
え？弱くない、だって
"Well, you aren't weak, I guess."
やーぽぽ！
"Yeah, both of us..."
オーケー！じゃあ、認めて！
"Okay then, admit it!"
自分のペット！
"That you're just our pet!"
私はペットじゃない！私はあなたのメンター！
"I am not your pet! I am your mentor!"
もくちゃん、私たち何かしないと！
"Mogu-chan, we have to do something!"
クイックグラブ！えい！
"Quick, grab 'em! Hah!"
もくちゃん何かして！
"Mogu-chan, do something!"
クイックグラブ！
"Quick grab!"
えい！えい！
"Hah! Hah!"
てい！これ！
"Take this! Take this!"
ストップ！ストレッチングミー！
"Stop stretching me out!"
何言ってるの！パドジャスティス！
"What do you say, Duo? I should be so nasty!"
絶対に謝らない！
"I'll never apologize!"
オッケー！じゃあ、これが最後のチャンス！
"Okay, well, this is your last chance!"
ダウナー！
"Take this! Down!"
え、こうダウンしたらだめ？
"You can't do down like this!"
ノットダウン！
"Not done!"
オッケー！じゃあ、ごめんなさい！
"Okay then, give it to her, then!"
わあ！わあ！
"Yay! Woo-hoo!"
ウェル、ダレスファン！
"Well, that was fun!"
ころねしゃぱーのね！
"Korone's got the knack!"
やあ！やあ！やあ！
"Yeah, yeah, yeah!"
もくちゃん！お互いペット欲しい、ね？
"Mogu-chan, what's the rule to get one's pet, okay?"
ペットのいいところは遊ぶこと！
"The best thing about having a pet is playing with them!"
パペプレイ！
"Puppy play!"
エキスポテト！もぐもぐ！
"Ekisupoteto! Mogu-mogu!"
誰かの気配...
"I feel someone's presence!"
誰かの気配、もしかして？
"Yeah, I feel someone's presence!"
ほら、人がいる！
"Look, people are here!"
にゃーにゃ！
"Nya-nya!"
わんわん！
"Wan-wan!"
とってもいい匂い！もくちゃん！
"It's such a good smell, Mogu-chan!"
キュートスメル！
"A cute smell!"
ころねせんぱい！おかゆせんぱい！
"Korone Senpai! Okayu Senpai!"
あいむ ころね あびすがあど！
"I am Korone Abisugado!"
あいむ おかか あびすがあど！
"I am Okayu Abisugado!"
アビスガードになりましたね！
"We became Abisugado!"
マッカイまで来てくれてありがとう！
"Thank you for coming all the way to Makkai!"
よかった！よかった！
"We're so glad!"
ENコンサートに呼んでくれてありがとう！
"Thank you for inviting us to the EN concert!"
コロロー、アビスガードと、おかかアビスガード！
"Kororo Abisugado and Okaka Abisugado!"
いらっしゃい！
"Irasshai!"
何やるんですか？4人じゃないとダメですか？
"What are we doing? Does it have to be four people?"
3人もできるらしいけど、4人のほうが...
"Three is possible, but four is more fun!"
ルールわからないけど、今度にする？
"We don't know the rules, but let's do it next time?"
今日、もくこと一緒に歌って踊りたいんですけど、いいですか？
"Today, Moku-ko, we want to sing and dance together, is that okay?"
いいよ！ベジージェスチャーね！
"Yes! Vegetable gesture, okay?"
みんなニャンニャンとワンワン一緒に！
"Let's all nyang-nyang and wan-wan together!"
君のyシャツの袖をめくったら チラリ見える線
When I rolled up the sleeve of your shirt, I caught a glimpse of that line.
不意打ち 高鳴る 胸の音にドキドキ
A surprise attack that made my heart throb and race!
「猫？ 猫？ にゃんにゃんにゃん ？ 犬 ？ 犬 ？ わんわんわん ？ 」
"Cat? Cat? Meow meow meow? Dog? Dog? Woof woof woof?"
「 猫 ！ 猫 ！ にゃんにゃんにゃん ！ 」
"Cat! Cat! Meow meow meow!"
(にゃんにゃる にゃんにゃる にゃる にゃんにゃんにゃん)
(Meow meow meow meow meow meow meow)
大福餅 ぽたぽた焼き うまいのは どっち です か ？
Daifuku mochi, pota-pota yaki—which one is more delicious?
僕 的 に は ササミジャーキー ！
For me, it's chicken jerky!
君のYシャツの袖をめくったら
When I pulled up the sleeve of your shirt,
チラリ見える線
a peek of skin was revealed.
不意打ち 高鳴る 胸の 音に ドキドキ
A surprise attack makes my heart race and throb!
猫？猫？にゃんにゃんにゃん？
Cat? Cat? Meow meow meow?
犬？犬？わんわんわん？
Dog? Dog? Woof woof woof?
猫！猫！にゃんにゃんにゃん！
Cat! Cat! Meow meow meow!
にゃんにゃにゃんにゃんにゃにゃんにゃん
(Meow-meow-meow-meow-meow-meow)
大福餅 ぽたぽた焼き
Daifuku mochi, pota-pota yaki,
ウマイのはどっちですか？
which one is more delicious?
僕はササミジャーキー！
For me, it's chicken jerky!
全然関係ないやいゃ～
That's completely unrelated, ya~
駆け抜けてく小春日和
Running through the Indian summer,
こんなに高いところに登りゃっちまった誰か助けて！
I climbed way up high. Someone, help!
にゃんにゃんにゃんこ。にゃんぽこら
Meow meow meow-kitty, nyan-pokora,
今日もゆく
I'm going today too.
チーズケーキ 豆乳プリン
Cheesecake, soy milk pudding,
ウマイのはどっちですか？
which one is tastier?
僕はミルクの骨！
For me, it's a milk bone!
良い子ぶってごめんねちゃい
Sorry for acting all innocent,
駆け寄ってくる「おかえりなさい」
running up with a "Welcome home!"
シッポが取れちゃう前に抱きしめてね
Hug me before my tail drops off!
犬！犬！わんわんわん！
Dog! Dog! Woof woof woof!
猫！猫！にゃんにゃんにゃん！
Cat! Cat! Meow meow meow!
犬！犬！わんわんわん！
Dog! Dog! Woof woof woof!
わんわらわんわらわんわんわん
(Woof-ruff-woof-ruff-ruff-woof-woof)
付けずっけきっとにゅうっぷり
Planted firmly with rich milk pudding—
ウマイのはどっちですか？
which one is more delicious?
僕はミルクの骨！
For me, it's a milk bone!
いい子ぶってごめんねちゃい
Sorry for acting all innocent!
鍵を降ろして お帰りなさい しっぽが取れちゃう前に
Lower the key, welcome home, before my tail falls off!
抱きしめてね ほりほりほりり
Hold me tight, digging away!
わんわんわん こわんぽこら
Woof woof woof, little wan-pokora,
今日もゆく
going today too.
待ち受け画面 お揃いね
Our lock screens match,
ペットにしたくなっちゃうよね
making me want you as my pet!
ベイビー嬉しいそうなアノ笑顔 ハマってしまいそう
Baby, that happy smile of yours has me hooked.
ぶるぶるしちゃう前に愛してよね… ね？
Love me before I start shivering... okay?
にゃんにゃんにゃん わんわん
Meow meow meow, woof woof!
犬派ですか？ 猫派ですか？
Are you a dog person? A cat person?
あなたはどっち派ですか？
Which one are you?
笑顔になる 魔法みたい
Like magic that brings a smile,
あなたと結ばれたんだ
I'm bound to you.
私のことナデナデして
Pet me and stroke me,
いつもギュッて おねんねしよう
and let's always cuddle to sleep.
仲良くしようね
Let's get along well!
にゃんにゃんにゃんこ。にゃんぽこら
Meow meow meow-kitty, nyan-pokora,
よろしくね
nice to meet you!
うちは、おかゆ先輩です！
For me, it's Okayu-senpai!
あの、おかゆ先輩です！
Um, Okayu-senpai!
そう、ツリータワー先輩！
Right, Tree Tower senpai!
ねこちゃね先輩、おかゆ先輩、とっても尊敬しています！
Okayu-senpai, we respect you so much!
今日一緒に踊ってくれてありがとう！
Thank you for dancing with us today!
ありがとう！ありがとう！
Thank you! Thank you!
ねえ、ぽこちゃん、いそいでアスク？アスクOK？
Hey, can I ask? Ask OK?
えっと、ハグしてもいいですか？
Um, can we get a hug?
おっけーおっけー！
Okay, okay!
ウェルカム！ウェルカム！
Welcome! Welcome!
てぇてぇ！尊い！
So precious! So precious!
ぽおぽお、ぽおぽおばあ！
Paw-paw, paw-paw bar!
バイバイ！バイバイ！
Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
モコちゃんも静まきゃーですごい！
Mococo is also super quiet, amazing!
え、おめおけーおけー！
Uh, meow, okay, okay!
After all that singing and dancing, my tummy's got a bit rumbly high.
Rumbly? Don't touch!
I'm a bit hungry.
Maybe we can go to that place.
And maybe get a bit of a special cheese! Special cheese!
And maybe get a bit of special cheese! Special cheese!
Ruffians, you'll come along with us, right?
Hi!
Okay!
Whatever!
Let's go, go!
We're here!
It's Akihabara!
It's Akihabara! Yeah!
BAU BAU! Yeah!
Look at all the buildings!
I can feel all of Akihabara's electronic energy right now! It's exciting!
Beep-beep-beep!
Well, you know, Akihabara has a bunch of different stores, so let's check them out! Yeah!
Over here!
We have our pharmacy! And it seems like right now, that Totsu Pharmacy is something that will help when your BAU BAU feels really rough.
I heard that it's been kind of tough recently, so if you need something, please go here!
And over here, we have YAGO, the arcade here in Akihabara! The latest and greatest games!
Uh, but hololo, I... I forgot my coin, so is it okay if it depends on you so that we can play some games together?
Well, next, let's take a look up there! We have Ramen, yeah!
You know, in case you need something to really fill you up, get ready to enjoy more of Akihabara!
Next, over here, over here, over here! We have the Pero Cafe!
I hear that they have some... some sort of suspicious and nasty maids, but I'm sure it's relaxing enough.
And you know, they have pet lights as well, in case you need something. And right beside it, there's Cover Denki for electronics, you know? They've been in Akihabara for a long time, so they're well-trusted!
And in this way, we have Game Island!
You know, there's lots of retro games, so I'm sure if there's something you're looking for, they have it!
And then back this way, yeah! We have the train!
The trains just go by BAU BAU! BAU BAU!
But we also have some light streetlights! I wonder why, huh? That's kind of strange.
But you know, when you're at Akihabara, you're most likely here for something really, really good!
Wow, let's check some of the Fuwamoco pictures, the howabous! BAU BAU!
First up, we have our 1st Anniversary Merch Complete Set!
It comes with the FUWAMOCO Happy Happi, which you can wear to represent FUWAMOCO, your favorite place!
We also have our BAU BAU Voice Keychain, so we can cheer you up wherever your paws take you!
Our Pero Plushie, which you can use as a good punching bag, of course!
Finally, we have our Pero Glass Set that you can use to enjoy a nice drink with your donut! Please check them out!
まず、FUWAMOCOの1周年記念グッズをご紹介します！
FUWAMOCOハッピー☆ハッピーを着たら、ラフィアンズだねって周りのみんながすぐわかるよ！
そして、BAU BAUボイスキーホルダー！ポチ一つでいつでもどこでもFUWAMOCOの声がすぐ聞けるよ！
ペロのぬいぐるみは、パンチングバッグとして使うしかない！
最後は、かわいいドーナツにぴったり合うFUWAMOCOのかわいいグラスセットです！ぜひゲットしてね！
Next, to commemorate our 3D debut today, we have our brand new FUWAMOCO Tail Keychain!
Now, this is the only time you're allowed to touch their tails however much you want, Ruffians!
These hang up these special 3D debut items from wherever you think looks best! Yay!
These are special 3D debut items to hang up wherever you think looks best! Yay!
次は3Dお披露目グッズです！こちらのフワモコのしっぽキーホルダーです！イェイ！
Next are the 3D debut goods! It's the FUWAMOCO tail keychain! Yay!
今回だけは許してくれるよ！このキーホルダーのキーホルダーしっぽ触れます！
Just for this time, you're allowed! You can touch this keychain's tail!
一番可愛いところに飾ってね！バイバーイ！
Display it in the cutest spot! Bye-bye!
That was... Fuwamoco Space!
I'm so excited for that! But...
What do we come here for again?
What did we come here for again?
Ah, Ruffian, do you remember it?
Ah, Ruffians, do you remember?
I'm hungry!
We're hungry!
As you know, if you come to Akiba, we need to get our favorite, right?
Donuts! Yay!
But you know, it looks like Fuwa forgot her coins, hi! You know, fluffy brain!
Bye-bye!
Ruffians, is it okay if you treat us to some donuts this time? We'll have it next time, okay? Please!
Can you give us a donut?
Please! Donuts!
Thank you! Thank you!
I got to take a bite, okay? Wait, wait. Mwah! Wait about Mococo, hi! So good!
I get to take a bite, okay? Wait, wait. Mwah! Wait about Mococo, hi! So good!
What about Mococo?
It's so good! Mwah!
Where is my donut? Hi! So tender! Me too!
Can I have a donut, please? More donuts, please! Me too!
Hi! Take it! Thank you! This time it's donuts!
Fuwawa's color! Okay! Hankwered! Hi!
This one tastes a little fluffy and line!
This one tastes a little fluffy and light!
It's a bit fuzzy and pink, hi! Mococo-chan!
I want to taste it too, can I have a bite? I guess we'll share a bite too?
It's a small one, okay?
Small, you promise? Just a small bite. You heard it, okay?
Okay, here you go!
You ate it! You ate it! But it's so fancy!
I get a bite now, hi! Mococo-chan, just a small bite.
Not as big as my bite, okay? I'll be fair!
Okay, here you go! Mwah!
Fuwawa, it was good, hi!
But you know, I still want more donuts! I only have one, so...
Fuwawa, I would like my donut. Donuts, donuts, donuts!
There's one more! There's one left!
Mococo-chan, you know, I've been looking forward to the donuts so much!
No, no, it's not fair! It has to be equal! No!
No! No! It's mine! It's mine! Well then, we only have one choice!
FUWAMOCO! Hi!
This is a wrestling ring!
This is Fuwamoco wrestling!
All the Ruffians!
Wow! Yay! Thank you! Oh my goodness!
Hello! Bye-bye! You're so cute!
It's fancy and so fluffy! Thank you! We can't wait to choose!
Fuwawa, I'll make sure that I beat up Mococo-chan a lot, okay?
No! I'm going to win, okay?
I'm going to do my best, okay?
Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
Well, Mococo-chan, I won't let you take that donut.
No, it's mine!
Stretch! Stretch!
Hi, let's get a bit more ready, Mococo! Take off the jackets!
Fuwawa! Already! Yeah! Hi!
Mococo! Already! Yeah! Hi!
I, the great Perocino, will be the referee for today's fight.
I guess we have a nasty referee for a nasty fight then, huh?
But it's going to be fair because... penalties here!
I, the boys, counts on that.
I, you boys, count on that.
Mococo-chan, it's my donut! Why was it not this time? It's mine, I'll win!
You have the last donut!
Oh my god!
I'm gonna win this time!
I never win!
I'll show you who's boss!
Spoiler warning, love's a bitch,
cuz you'll just break up
Then someday, you'll close your eyes
and never wake up
What the? That's so meaningful and cool...
I'm dancing with a word book like that. So long
Tu tulu tu tu tulu ish
Mococo-chan!
It doesn't have to be like this!
You could just give me the donut, you know?
No, it's mine!
I'm not gonna let you back seat this, okay?
That's enough,
that's enough
That's enough, that's enough. I'm getting excited, on the contrary
It's big, it's big, your dream
It's big, it's big
The economy's good, but quality's the end
Yay, yay
"Gott ist tot"
Mococo-chan, get out of the way!
No, it's my donut!
Fuwawa, get out of the way!
Now I'm gonna chew you up!
No! No!
Fuwawa, get out of the way!
No, it's my donut!
That's god-ish, unfair, that's god-ish, "My god"
I want you, want you. Feels like my IQ's dropping
That's wicked-hearted, after all, that's wicked-hearted, "My god"
I hate you, hate you. Which one of us is the pest?
That hair style, those eyes, those lips
That perfume, those clothes, that make-up
They're that-ish, compare, they're that-ish
That witty remark, that opinion, that critique
That charisma, that gag, that sense
They're god-ish, unfair
"-ish", "-ish", "-ish", I adore it!
Tu tulu tu tu tulu "ish"
It's "ish", yeah? It's "ish", yeah?
Tu tulu tu tu tulu / God-ish
Mococo-chan!
It doesn't have to be like this!
You could just give me the donut, you know?
No, it's mine!
One, two, three, go!
Mococo-chan, don't think you can get away from me!
I am just the perfect date!
No, I called the power spot!
He go, he go, hello!
Is the essence of meta-thinking malice?
An artifice that looks down on others
It's hard to survive in idleness. The light wavers
Denying god and taking the place of god...
...the small fry suddenly change on the throne
A prayer of self-discipline disguised as criticism
Do you know?
What're you saying? That's so annoying.
What're you saying?
I dunno what that means. I'm gonna fall asleep, seriously
I'm easily bored. OK.
Everyone's easily bored. OK.
Gimme something I can dance with, gimme, beam...
That's so gross, that's so gross
I've become a fan, on the contrary
You're small, you're small,
you're small-minded
You're small, you're small
Lonely because you're a genius. How cool... How cool...
"Gott ist tot"
That's god-ish, unfair, that's god-ish, "My god"
It's like dropping dead while insisting, "I'm healthy, super healthy"
That sounds desperate, in the end, that sounds desperate, "My god"
How sorrowful, how sorrowful, epigone's heel
That title, that art, that story
That music, that song, that melody
They're that-ish, compare, they're that-ish
That witty remark, that opinion, that critique
That charisma, that gag, that sense
They're god-ish, unfair
"-ish", "-ish", "-ish", I adore it!
Tu tulu tu tu tulu "ish"
It's "ish", yeah? It's "ish", yeah?
Tu tulu tu tu tulu / God-ish
Mococo-chan!
I don't think you can get away from me!
No! I'll win!
I'll show you who's boss!
One, two, three, go!
Mococo-chan, don't think you can get away from me!
I am just the perfect date!
Spoiler warning, love's a bitch, cuz you'll just break up
Then someday, you'll close your eyes and never wake up
What the? That's so meaningful and cool...
I'm dancing with a word book like that. So long
Tu tulu tu tu tulu "ish"
It's "ish", yeah? It's "ish", yeah?
Tu tulu tu tu tulu / God-ish
Mococo-chan!
It doesn't have to be like this!
You could just give me the donut, you know?
No, it's mine!
One, two, three, go!
Mococo-chan, don't think you can get away from me!
I am just the perfect date!
No, I called the power spot!
He go, he go, hello!
That's enough, that's enough
That's enough, that's enough. I'm getting excited, on the contrary
It's big, it's big, your dream
It's big, it's big
Ass-kick you!
Mococo, I found a chair!
I found a, I'm gonna use it!
Mogojohn, Mogojohn!
Mogojohn, it's just a plastic toy!
You can't win against this!
Ha! This is a magical weapon, okay?
Ha! Let's see how good it is, Dad!
Mogojohn! Mogojohn!
Mogojohn! Mogojohn! Mogojohn!
Mogojohn! Mogojohn! No!
One, two, four!
Escort! Escort!
What do you say, Mogojohn? Did you give up?
Yes! Yes! Yes! The Bau! Bau!
I'm the winner!
A place so high... Plug it up!
It's okay. I won. Take my hand. No! It's okay.
Are you sure? Yeah, yeah. High five! Oh my!
I'm the winner, right? I guess I'll get my donut later then, huh?
When you lose, you get punishment! I'm not a loser!
No, no, the punishment! Mococo is the punishment!
The ruffians have a special embarrassing line they want you to say!
What do you mean, not good? Fuwawa is too embarrassing, so goy... goy...
Do you have to? That's what the ruffians want, okay? Do your best!
Okay. You wouldn't mind a... Sloggy doggy sweaty hug from Fuwawa, would you?
Or my little bow-chump after all! Come here!
Mogojohn, can't see you! Ah, I can't see you! It's too bad, huh?
The ruffians like... there are things like that hard... with you, it could've been more butts to kick for Fuwawa, right?
I think so. As long as it means that we can protect each other, right?
Well, if it's okay, I feel a little bit more comfy with my jacket.
This is good, huh? Which is better?
You know we did a bunch of pro wrestling here. And there's some crazy things that can happen here.
So, next, let's sing another song! Okay, please listen to Psycho Marumatsu Keikaku!
ねぇ 聴こえてる?
Hey, can you hear me?
きみと共にギリギリなファイト
A desperate fight alongside you
あからさまにミゼラブルなファイト
An overt, miserable fight
ラヴはいつもアナキズムなファイト
Love is always an anarchic fight
わたしだけのインモラルなファイト
An immoral fight that belongs only to me
さよなら 言えない わたしは ダメだな
I can't say goodbye, I'm so useless
わからない わからない 自分が わからない
I don't know, I don't know, I don't understand myself
この気持ち 消そうもない こんなにも なくならない
This feeling won't fade away, it won't disappear at all
いけないんだと 思えば 思う程 加速するの
The more I think I shouldn't, the more it accelerates
もう自分自身が 怖いけど 今信じてみるよ
I'm already scared of myself, but now I'll try to believe
何を 失っても きみの御許に と決めたの
No matter what I lose, I've decided to be by your side
聴いて アイ キャン ノット ストップ ビコーズ アイ ラヴ ユー
Listen! I can not stop because I love you
たとえ 明日になれば
Even if tomorrow comes
アイ キャン ノット ストップ ビコーズ アイ ウォント ユー
I can not stop because I want you
消えゆく 運命でも
Even in a fading destiny
アイ キャン ノット ストップ ビコーズ アイ メット ユー
I can not stop because I met you
わたしを止める
What stops me
アイ キャン ノット ストップ ビコーズ アイ ニード ユー
I can not stop because I need you
理由にもならないよ
It's not even a reason
わたし きみの前なら インモラリストだよ
In front of you, I'm an immoralist
ねぇ 聴こえてる?
Hey, can you hear me?
きみと共にギリギリなファイト
A desperate fight alongside you
あからさまにミゼラブルなファイト
An overt, miserable fight
ラヴはいつもアナキズムなファイト
Love is always an anarchic fight
わたしだけのインモラルなファイト
An immoral fight that belongs only to me
悲しみ 苦しみ 憎しみ おいでよ
Sadness, suffering, hatred, come on
わたしは いつでも 迎える 覚悟さ
I am always prepared to welcome them
そんなふうに 思えるようにもなったの 不思議だな
I've come to be able to think that way, how strange
出逢ってくれて ありがとう わたし 少し強くなれた
Thank you for meeting me, I've become a little stronger
涙なんて 神様にあげるから
I'll give my tears to God
だから お願い 自由を下さい
So please, give me freedom
どこにでもゆける 翼を
Wings that can go anywhere
アイ ウォント トゥ ビー ウィズ ユー フォーエヴァー
I want to be with you forever
たとえ かなうはずもない
Even if it's bound to never come true
アイ ウォント トゥ ビー ウィズ ユー フォーエヴァー
I want to be with you forever
何かに 襲われても
Even if attacked by something
アイ ウォント トゥ ビー ウィズ ユー フォーエヴァー
I want to be with you forever
この 手を 離さないで
Don't let go of this hand
アイ ウォント トゥ ビー ウィズ ユー フォーエヴァー
I want to be with you forever
そばに いてよ
Stay by my side
一歩だって引かないよ
I won't back down even a step
わたし きみの前なら ヒロイックだよ
In front of you, I'm heroic
ただ ただ 愛したいのに
I just, just want to love
ただ ただ 苦しくてさ
I just, just suffer so much
この わたしの インモラル 一人で抱えるには 少し重すぎるの
This immorality of mine is a bit too heavy to carry alone
もういいっそのこと 全て 捨ててしまおう なんて
Murmuring that I should just throw everything away
呟いて 眠るけれど いつも きみの夢ばかり
I fall asleep, but it's always dreams of you
あぁ 答え なんて 出なくても 立ち向かうよ
Ah, even if no answer comes out, I'll face it
そう これは もう わたし の こころ からだ 全てが
Yes, this is my heart, my body, everything
きみとね 出逢って 導き出した 答え
The answer I deduced after meeting you
止まらない 止まれない 止まるつもりもない
I won't stop, I can't stop, I have no intention of stopping
きみの御許に と決めたの きみのため 今戦うの
I've decided to be by your side, fighting for you now
理由にもならないよ
It's not even a reason
わたし きみの前なら インモラリストだよ
In front of you, I'm an immoralist
ねぇ 聴こえてる?
Hey, can you hear me?
きみと共にギリギリなファイト
A desperate fight alongside you
あからさまにミゼラブルなファイト
An overt, miserable fight
ラヴはいつもアナキズムなファイト
Love is always an anarchic fight
わたしだけのインモラルなファイト
An immoral fight that belongs only to me
相撲 相撲 相撲 相撲 ももももも
Sumo, sumo, sumo, sumo, momomomomo
ああ 相撲 取らなきゃ 時は過ぎゆけば 相撲ももももも
Ah, if we don't do sumo, time passes by, sumo momomomomo
しなやかに 二人の愛が実ります
Gracefully, our love will bear fruit
雨降りの証と言いましょう
Let's call it proof of a rainy day
相撲も ももももも 最強の思想
Sumo, momomomomo, the strongest ideology
この世のために残しましょう
Let's leave it behind for this world
たったひとつのこのミサを
This one and only mass
相撲も 相撲も あなたさまへ
Sumo, sumo, to you, my lord
捧げます
I offer it
相撲ももももも ももももも おす
Sumo, momomomomo, momomomomo, oshi
ふわふわ もこもこ 魔界の番犬シスターズ
Fuwawa, Mococo, Underworld Watchdog Sisters
この世界に爆誕"BAU"DOLです
We are the bombastic "BAU"DOLs born into this world!
BAU BAU ふわふわ もこもこ
BAU BAU Fuwawa, Mococo
Wake upしたら 君にMorning
When I wake up, morning to you
Newな出会い 秘密のサイン キャッチして
New encounters, catching secret signs
ドキドキドキ 右に左
Thumping, thumping, right and left
ポンポンポン 悩んでいても
Pong pong pong, even when worrying
きちゃうFuture 目の前の道 Stepして
Future coming, stepping on the path ahead
Happy Lucky Puppy 一緒に歩こうよ
Happy Lucky Puppy, let's walk together
ドーナツの 穴の中には
Inside the hole of a donut
きっと
Surely,
surely,
夢が詰まってるから
dreams are packed inside.
ふわふわ
Fuwafuwa,
もこもこ
mokomoko,
魔界乃番犬シスターズ☆★
Makai no Banken Sisters☆★
2匹が揃えばもう大騒ぎ
When two of us get together, it's already chaotic!
もがもが
Mogamoga,
ハロハロ
Halo halo,
迷わずにGo my way
without hesitating, Go my way.
君の絶対味方 “BAU”DOLです
Your absolute ally, it's "BAU"DOL!
BAU BAU
ふわふわ
Fuwafuwa,
もこもこ
mokomoko,
FUWA＋MOCOは FUWAMOCO
FUWA＋MOCO is FUWAMOCO!
ふわふわ
Fuwafuwa,
もこもこ
mokomoko,
FUWA＋MOCOは FUWAMOCO
FUWA＋MOCO is FUWAMOCO!
ひとりじゃないよWe’re together
You're not alone, We're together.
ハートつながってる君とChatして
Chatting with you, our hearts connected,
Fluffy Fuzzy Yappy 一緒に歌おうよ
Fluffy Fuzzy Yappy, let's sing together!
ドーナツの穴の向こうへ
Beyond the hole of the donut...
きっと
Surely,
surely,
君が待っているから
because you are waiting for us!
ふわふわ
Fuwafuwa,
もこもこ
mokomoko,
魔界乃番犬シスターズ☆★
Makai no Banken Sisters☆★
2匹が揃えばもう止まらない
When two of us get together, there's no stopping us!
お耳も
Ears too,
尻尾も
tail too,
お触りは厳禁××
touching is strictly prohibited××!
スリル満点爆弾 “BAU”DOLです
Thrill-packed bomb, it's "BAU"DOL!
Hey!! RUFFIANS!!
Kept you waiting, huh?
Can I get a heck yeah!?
Let's shout “BAU”!!
BAU!! BAU!! BAU!! Now, hear the howling of my soul!!
Are you ready?!
Moco-chan!! この曲は可愛く歌おうねって言ったでしょ!!
Moco-chan!! I said we should sing this song cute!!
bau bau
じゃあBメロから…せーの！
Well then, from the B melody... Ready, set!
ドーナツリングに誓って
Swearing on the donut ring,
ずっと
always,
笑顔を守るから
we will protect your smile!
ふわふわ
Fuwafuwa,
もこもこ
mokomoko,
魔界乃番犬シスターズ☆★
Makai no Banken Sisters☆★
2匹が揃えばもう大騒ぎ
When two of us get together, it's already chaotic!
もがもが
Mogamoga,
ハロハロ
Halo halo,
迷わずにGo my way
without hesitating, Go my way.
君の絶対味方 “BAU”DOLです
Your absolute ally, it's "BAU"DOL!
この世界に爆誕 “BAU”DOLです
Born into this world, it's "BAU"DOL!
BAU BAU
ふわふわ
Fuwafuwa,
もこもこ
mokomoko,
FUWA＋MOCOは FUWAMOCO
FUWA＋MOCO is FUWAMOCO!
ふわふわ
Fuwafuwa,
もこもこ
mokomoko,
FUWA＋MOCOは FUWAMOCO
FUWA＋MOCO is FUWAMOCO!
BAUBAU～！！
BAUBAU～!!
Wow... Thank you so much, guys!
That was our brand new original song, "Born to be BAU"DOL"!
(Waah! Wow! Wait, did you think it was cute?)
We hope you enjoyed "Born to be BAU"DOL" along with our singing and smiling!
Fuwafuwa mokomoko, just like that!
You know it's such a fun and energetic song, and the dancing makes it even more fun, right?
So we hope that you'll dance it together with us too, okay? Please!
But you know what? I'm exhausted! You know, donuts, pro wrestling, singing and dancing...
It's been exhausting! We had so much fun that I can't believe our live was so short!
Aw, maybe it's time to go home. Aw, okay.
You know, it's always a little bit hard to say goodbye, but we'll be back soon, right? For sure!
Yeah, you could never stay away from Akihabara for very long, right? So much stuff to see!
Yeah! Okay Moco-chan, let's go home!
Bau bau!!
stop ほしくずで髪を飾り
Stop decorating my hair with stardust
non-stop 優しい目を待つわプールサイド
Non-stop, waiting for your gentle eyes by the poolside
zuki-zuki 切なくふるえる胸
Throbbing, my chest trembles with pain
幻でもいい 逢いたいのに
Even if it's just a fantasy, I want to see you
heart on wave
あなたは来ない
You don't come
私の思慕をジョークにしないで
Don't turn my longing into a joke
lonely ゆらゆら swimmin' ゆらゆら dreamin'
Lonely, swaying while swimming, swaying while dreaming
愛が揺れる stop stop
Stop the love that shakes me
heart on wave
あなたは来ない
You don't come
私の思慕をジョークにしないで
Don't turn my longing into a joke
love 花柄の水着だけが
Love, only my floral swimsuit
love me 目立ちすぎて泣きたくなるの
Love me, it stands out so much I want to cry
jiri-jiri 焦げてるこの痛みを
Jiri-jiri, this burning pain
冷たい水辺に そっと浮かべて
I'll gently float on the cold waterside
heart on wave
泳ぎ出すけれど
I start to swim, but
あなたの理想には追いつけなくて
I can't keep up with your ideal
i can't ねえ こんなに苦しいのに
I can't, hey, even though it hurts so much
なぜ なぜ あなたじゃなきゃダメなの
Why, why do I need you and no one else?
lonely ゆらゆら swimmin' ゆらゆら dreamin'
Lonely, swaying while swimming, swaying while dreaming
愛が揺れる stop stop
Stop the love that shakes me
heart on wave
あなたは来ない
You don't come
私の思慕をジョークにしないで
Don't turn my longing into a joke
jiri-jiri 焦げてるこの痛みを
Jiri-jiri, this burning pain
冷たい水辺に そっと浮かべて
I'll gently float on the cold waterside
heart on wave
泳ぎ出すけれど
I start to swim, but
あなたの理想には追いつけなくて
I can't keep up with your ideal
i can't ねえ こんなに苦しいのに
I can't, hey, even though it hurts so much
なぜ なぜ あなたじゃなきゃダメなの
Why, why do I need you and no one else?
lonely ゆらゆら swimmin' ゆらゆら dreamin'
Lonely, swaying while swimming, swaying while dreaming
愛が揺れる stop stop
Stop the love that shakes me
heart on wave
あなたは来ない
You don't come
私の思慕をジョークにしないで
Don't turn my longing into a joke
i can't ねえ こんなに苦しいのに
I can't, hey, even though it hurts so much
なぜ なぜ あなたじゃなきゃダメなの
Why, why do I need you and no one else?
lonely ゆらゆら swimmin' ゆらゆら dreamin'
Lonely, swaying while swimming, swaying while dreaming
愛が揺れる stop stop
Stop the love that shakes me
heart on wave
あなたは来ない
You don't come
私の思慕をジョークにしないで
Don't turn my longing into a joke
heart on wave
あなたは来ない
You don't come
私の思慕をジョークにしないで
Don't turn my longing into a joke
lonely ゆらゆら swimmin' ゆらゆら dreamin'
Lonely, swaying while swimming, swaying while dreaming
愛が揺れる stop stop
Stop the love that shakes me
heart on wave
あなたは来ない
You don't come
私の思慕をジョークにしないで
Don't turn my longing into a joke
lonely ゆらゆら swimmin' ゆらゆら dreamin'
Lonely, swaying while swimming, swaying while dreaming
愛が揺れる stop stop
Stop the love that shakes me
Thank you! Thank you!
Oh, we're back in the forest! Let's, let's pass it! Whoa!
Sister quickly said, it's so beautiful and nighttime, right?
Oh, we really wanted to share this view together with you.
It's been a long time that we waited for, right?
And today we're able to sing the songs that we really love here for you.
Now, in the place that we grew up, it means so much to us.
But you know, we're no longer puppies, so you know, we're FUWAMOCO!
Hello, puppies!
Hah! Hah!
Actually, there's that thing, right, Mococo?
Oh! There's something we wanted to tell you!
It's okay if we go on ahead, right?
Let's go! Let's go!
Oh, boy! Oh, boy!
We're here, right under the Tree of Prominence!
The Tree of Prominence!
It's a very special tree to us demon dogs, but especially us demon guardogs!
And you know, we'd like to sing our last song for today right here!
Right here!
You know, and this song means so much to us because it's all for you.
You know, all of it. Everything is for you.
Thank you so much, always.
Well, please listen to our last song for today.
きみがため
For your sake...
きみの瞳に映る わたしは何色ですか
What color am I, reflected in your eyes?
赤深き望むなら 渡そう陽の光を
If you deeply desire red, I will bestow upon you the sunlight.
悲しみが溢れ 瞼閉じました
Sorrow overflowed, and I closed my eyelids;
こぼれた滴は 心に沁みゆく
The spilled teardrops soak deep into my heart.
行き渡る波は 弱く交えます
The permeating waves gently intertwine,
悲しみが溢れ
Sorrow overflowed,
瞼閉じました
and I closed my eyelids;
こぼれた滴は
The spilled teardrops
心に沁みゆく
soak deep into my heart.
行き渡る波は
The permeating waves
弱く交えます
gently intertwine,
とどけしゆりかご 眠りをさそう
A reaching cradle invites slumber.
夢に なつかし 面影をさがす 手を伸ばし 強く 抱きしめたくなる
In my dreams, I search for a nostalgic trace of you, reaching out my hand, wanting to hold you tight.
きみの瞳に映る わたしは何色ですか
What color am I, reflected in your eyes?
藍深き望むなら 渡そう高き空を
If you deeply desire indigo, I will bestow upon you the high sky.
歓びが溢れ 巡りあいました
Joy overflowed, and we met by chance,
こぼれおつ笑みは 別れを隠す
The overflowing smile hides our parting.
人はいつしか 朽ち果てるけれど
Though humans will surely wither away one day,
唄となり 語り継がれてゆくでしょう
surely our song will become a tale passed down through generations.
きみの瞳に映る わたしは何色ですか
What color am I, reflected in your eyes?
わたしは何色ですか 緑深き望むなら
What color am I? If you deeply desire green...
緑深き 望むなら
If you wish for a deep green,
渡そう この大地を
then I shall give you the very earth.
もろく 儚きものよ
Oh, fragile, fleeting ones,
強く 美しきものよ
oh, strong, beautiful ones,
あるがまま ha-
be as you are. Ah...
きみの瞳に映る
Reflected in your eyes,
わたしは何色ですか
what color am I?
安らぎを 覚えたなら
If you remember peace,
そこに わたしはいる
then I shall be there.
きみの瞳に映る
Reflected in your eyes,
わたしは何色ですか
what color am I?
うら深き 望むなら
If you wish for the deep past,
渡そう この想いを
then I shall give you my feelings.
渡そう このすべてを
Then I shall give you everything of me.
Ah, thank you so much for this!
Thank you!
You know, we're not the best at expressing our feelings to you.
Today is a special day!
So you know, we did our best,
and well, we wrote some letters for you.
Is it okay?
Do you want to hear them?
Okay!
Wow, I'll go first then, okay?
Dear Ruffians, thank you for all the fluffy headpats, for all your warmth, and for always being here for me during this past year.
I never would have dreamed that I could be standing here right now, having already done so many amazing things a little more than a year from the day we met,
but here I am, and it's truly thanks to you.
There have been so many sunny days and some rainy ones too, but they've all been special and full of meaning because you were there by my side.
Thank you from the bottom of my heart.
Please continue to share that beautiful smile of yours with me lots and lots, and I'll make sure that nothing can lay a paw on it! Okay?
Sincerely, your fluffy Fuwawa~ Bau Bau!
Bau Bau!
Ah, next, Mococo-chan's turn!
My turn? I guess it's my turn then. Hi! I'll do my best! Hi!
Dear Ruffians,
I can't believe we're finally here, after so long, I'm so...
I'm so happy we've been able to spend today together.
To be honest, there were many hard times, times when we doubted ourselves and were frustrated with our own limits,
but because you were here by my side with kind words and lots of headpats...
because you accepted me even when I was maybe a bit needy or being silly, we were able to reach today!
There's still a lot of growing I have to do, but I hope you can watch me do my best and take even one step forward everyday.
Because you know, one step forward a day is 7 steps a week! And eventually, that will amount to something amazing.
And of course, I will always be waiting here for you, ready to protect your smile! Nothing will ever break the pledge we made to you.
So get ready, because your smile is going to be protected, whether you like it or not! Got it?
Sincerely, your fluffy Mococo~ Bau Bau!
Bau Bau!
Today, another huge dream of ours has come true.
Thank you so much!
Always... please let us continue to protect your smiles forever and ever, okay? Forever and ever!
Bau Bau!
これからもよろしくね！
Here's to working together from now on!
Bau Bau!